Michal Przekop

contact

przekop.michal@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://mprzekop.github.io/Portfolio/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/micha%C5%82-przekop-994762188/

GitHub: https://github.com/MPrzekop

Profile

Unity generalist with experience working in small agile teams and developing for the Nintendo Switch system and PC. Lately, in my free time, I have been focusing more on a technical art aspect and tool making for the Unity engine, to see what can be achieved when you expand or replace solutions provided by Unity.

Work experience

Game Planet (July 2020 - Currently), Software Engineer

I worked on *Restaurant Renovation* - a casual "simulator" style Steam title, and provided systems for teams developing other titles.

- Gameplay: Developed character creator, modular first-person controller, skill system, player interactions, task system, and UI.
- Engine: Implemented real-time texture painting for stain/dirt removal, and serialization system.
- Tools: Provided systems and interfaces for authoring gameplay-ready assets and scenes.

Gdansk University of Technology (October 2019 - January 2020), Lecturer

I gave lectures for high schoolers about 3D graphics and game development as a part of the "Akademia ETI" program.

Creative Forge S.A. (June 2019 - September 2020), Designer, Software Engineer

I worked on the trailer and gameplay prototypes for the Far Fetched Steam game.

- Gameplay: Prototyped several iterations of a character controller that heavily focused on the character's movement feel and natural animation inertia.
- Graphics: Implemented a shader with a highly customizable lighting model. Created shaders for natural foliage movement and interactions. Developed customizable outline post-process.
- Engine: Provided optimized, interactive instanced particle system.
- Tools: Created tools for in-engine authoring grass and stone assets.

Forever Entertainment S.A. (July 2018 - February 2019), Software Engineer

I worked mainly as a Unity Generalist on the *We are the Plague* title. Ported *Fly O'Clock* (Unity), *Grab Lab* (Unity) from mobile, and *Bad Dream Fever* (Game Maker 2), from PC to Nintendo Switch system. And helped to create a map import tool for *Rise Eterna*.

• Gameplay: Worked on player/team controller, inventory, and dialogue systems for a turn-based tactical RPG. Implemented local multiplayer for the *Fly O'Clock* port.

- Engine: Helped to implement and optimized AI and animation systems for a turn-based tactical RPG. Ported gameplay, UI, and input system, for the Nintendo Switch. Ported visual effects from Nintendo Switch to PC.
- Mentoring: Helped members of the internship program with bug fixing and Unity best practices.

Experience

C#, C++, HLSL, Unity, Amplify Shader Editor, Shadergraph, Unity HDRP, Unity built-in pipeline, Git, Trello

Education

Bachelor of Science, computer science, Gdansk University of Technology (2015-2019)

Additional

President of science club "Vertex" at GUT (October 2017 - June 2020)

I lead a science club that served as a platform for education and cooperation in game development, computer graphics, and virtual reality.